Itsuka, that's impossible!
I-Itsuka crossed the finish line
before you pushed...
That's so lame.
Shido...
What's going on?
Shido!
Spirits. Special designation disaster
beings that exist in a critical space.
Approach 1: Annihilate them by military force.
Approach 2: Date them and
make them fall in love.
"Episode Twelve:
'Make Shido Itsuka Swoon'"
My body's... burning....
Emergency analysis shows...
The path between all you and Shin
has drastically narrowed...
...which is hindering
circulation of Spirit powers.
Basically, all that Spirit power is
causing Shido's body to overheat.
I see... Since it has nowhere to go,
it's giving Shido incredible powers.
Yeah, but it's possible he'll go on a rampage
with all eight of our Spirit powers.
That would be terrible!
What can we do to save Shido?!
The answer is simple.
Kiss him. That's it.
Kiss?
All of you kissing Shin will open the path
for Spirit power to flow again.
Your time limit is 12 tonight.
B-By 12...
...we have to kiss Shido...
Kissing Shido to save him
is like the icing on the cake.
Bad news, Commander!
Shido escaped from the infirmary!
Shido Itsuka?!
A woman...?
It's a woman... Gotta make her fall for me...
That's my duty after all.
I've missed you so much, Ellen!
What in the world happened here?
You don't think Shido did this...?
Wonder. Such Spirit power...
Luckily, we know where he is by the monitor.
We'll head straight there.
How can you be doing this?!
You're inside my Territory!
Don't be so hostile, Ellen.
I just want us to understand one another.
This joke of yours isn't funny.
I'm not joking though.
Forget Ratatoskr and DEM.
We can still love one another.
Ellen, it's you that I--
Enough of this!
Don't cause me too much trouble now.
Bye-bye.
My cute Ellen.
How humiliating! You'll pay
for this, Shido Itsuka!
Ah, my body's light as a feather.
I feel great! Everyone's power
is surging inside me!
I love you!
I want you!
I need you!
The sky is blue!
And my heart is clear and bright!
Shido!
Hey, Tohka! Kotori! Everyone!
Have you all come to see me?
Listen up, Shido. We've come to save you.
Save me?
Yeah? You all want to kiss me?
Yes! With an especially passionate smooch!
All right.
Though, I'll kinda regret losing this power...
However, there's a condition!
What condition?
Listening. Let's hear it then.
I made all of you fall for me
in order to seal your powers.
This time, you have to make me fall for you.
Wha...?
Huh?
But to be honest, I already
like all of you guys as it is.
So to say "Make me fall for you"
is a bit off the mark.
Use whatever method you want.
Make my heart skip a beat.
Enough that I can't wait to kiss you. Yeah?
Make his heart skip a beat?
Enough that he'll want to kiss us?
So be it. Ratatoskr will go
all-out to make you fall for us.
What an honor.
Let me know once you're ready.
Then let's get started... and begin our date!
Our time limit is 12 o'clock.
We have until then to...
Shido...
Is this the place? Let's see what you've got.
Shido!
Shido.
Darling!
You look lovely, everyone.
You went out and picked swimsuits
just for me? Thank you.
Yeah, of course.
Caution. What are you falling for him for?
Shido's supposed to do that.
Huh? I know that!
Ratatoskr presents...
The one and only heart-throbbing
Fall in Love Dome!
Fall in Love Dome?
Allow me to explain the rules!
The Spirits will take turns...
...trying to make Shido's heart
skip a beat in their own way.
We'll be closely monitoring Shido's
excitement level here in the control room!
And once it exceeds a certain level...!
...you'll hear a fanfare like this
which signals a triumph!
Kissing Shido will come after
everyone completes their turn.
The time limit is 12 o'clock tonight!
Do I make myself clear, everyone?!
Let's get one thing straight, Kannazuki.
This isn't the time to screw
around with our choices.
Of course not, Commander!
Your unworthy dog, Kyouhei Kannazuki,
will surmount Shido whatever it takes!
That wording sorta puts me off...
I have something to say.
If we're using a beach, why isn't it
nudist like I originally suggested?
Eh?
Nudist?
If our goal is to excite Shido,
it's more effective to catch him off guard.
If everyone here was naked, we'd already
be hearing the fanfare by now.
Th-That might be true, but there's
certain things we can and can't do!
I get what you're saying, Origami,
but that may have the opposite effect.
His shock might exceed the excitement.
I see. Then I'll strip bit by bit.
That's the way to do it!
That's not the way, but...
The vice commander and Origami
sure make a good combo.
Seems like they're always
on the same wavelength.
Must be all those hobbies they share.
Now then! Let's get this
conquest of Shido underway!
Do we have any volunteers?!
A true warrior is first to the battle!
Shall we get this ball rolling?
Pride. Leave this to Kaguya and me.
Whoa! The Yamai Sisters are first up to bat!
That's the Hurricane Children for you!
Rushing forth like the wind!
Two girls at once, huh?
Be gentle with me please. Kaguya... Yuzuru...
Prepare yourself, Shido.
We'll make you fall for us.
For sure. KO in one round.
"1: Surround Shido on both sides
and touch him with a squeeze attack.
2: Sneak a vanilla-flavored kiss using an ice cream cone. 3: Ride Shido together like he's a human banana boat."
"1: Surround Shido on both sides
and touch him with a squeeze attack.
2: Sneak a vanilla-flavored kiss using an ice cream cone. 3: Ride Shido together like he's a human banana boat."
Here we go.
"3: Ride Shido together like
he's a human banana boat."
Your choices, everyone!
Hmm, one or two?
Aww! But what about choice three?!
Strap a rope around his neck!
Hear that, you two?! Go with three
and ride Shido like a human--
"Ratatoskr presents"
"Fall in Love"
"Dome event"
"Sorry
Please wait"
Uh, what are you doing, guys?
A coup d'état? Revolution?!
The commander gave orders to tie you up
if you started screwing around!
Oh, what a commander!
In that case, tie me up tighter!
What are you doing?!
The left side is way too slack!
--What's that idiot doing?
--Hold on! You're doing it wrong!
--I guess that means it's number two
and the squeeze attack then.
--Hold on! You're doing it wrong!
--I guess that means it's number two
and the squeeze attack then.
--Ah, I can't believe this!
What's up, you two?
How's that, Shido?
Don't our charms make your heart flutter?
Agreement. It's no use
trying to lie to yourself.
There... There!
Hey now, I like it, but you girls should
hold off on this stuff till you're married.
Wha...?
Shock. Shido's not fazed in the slightest.
But thank you anyway.
You're both trying so hard for me.
I appreciate the thought.
Sh-Shido...
Blush. I feel cheated for some reason...
No, cheer up a bit.
He may look composed, but Shin's
excitement level is climbing.
Try out two this time.
What gives?
You went to get ice cream but
only for yourselves? I'm sad...
Heh, a hasty conclusion, Shido!
Bestow. One of these is for you.
One will be plenty for Kaguya and me.
Oh, thanks.
Sweetness...
I can't hold back...
Sorry to disturb you, but...
...weren't you supposed to do that
with Shin and not with each other?
Eh?
Neglect. Now that you mention it...
Oh...
Huh?
Coldness!
Hurray! Today's very first fanfare!
Yamai Sisters! You made him fall for you!
My goodness. You got me good.
Eh? Next up is Natsumi?
You volunteered all on
your own? Why, thank you.
Yeah right. The rest of us drew straws.
This condition of yours is absurd...
The others might be able to manage,
but to make you fall for me?
It's not even possible.
That's not true at all.
You're plenty cute, Natsumi.
I-I can't do it! Hold on a sec!
Hmm?
Hey, let's do some multiplayer!
Okay, sure!
Wait, but Natsumi doesn't even own the game.
She can play by herself then.
You knew I didn't own the game
from the very start, you big jerks!
Now I've got him...
Natsumi, it's too dangerous
to be using Spirit power right now.
Revert back at once.
It'll be fine. I'm using a real swimsuit.
He'll fall for me quick anyway.
Hi, Shido. Sorry to keep you.
Natsumi, your body is...
Oh, Shido, I know you're
interested in a big girl's body.
Huh?
Another success!
Natsumi's baggy swimsuit for the win!
Seriously?
Yoshino, your suit...
Oh, no worries. Yoshino?
Yoshino scores a success!
Hey now, this is a whole
different mood than before.
Having just the beach is boring, right?
But from here on out,
it's adult time. Elegant time.
They say boys grow up quickly, don't they?
But a lady can change
in the moment you look away.
Understand, big brother?
That's my commander! Success!
Darling?
Tonight, I want to...
...sing a song just for you.
Miku success!
Huh? But I haven't even sung yet!
Hey. Next up is you, hmm?
Shido...
No liquor, okay?
No problem. It's alcohol-free.
Something the matter?
I don't know anymore.
Know what?
Forget it.
Cheers.
It's alcohol-free all right.
What's wrong, Origami?
Itsuka...
How is it that you're so handsome?
Itsuka? Wait... You're the Origami from then?
Does it really make a difference?
Whenever I think about you,
it makes me all fuzzy inside...
And my heart gets all tight...
Itsuka, I love... I love you!
I love you so much, I don't know what to do!
Origami success!
That's seven of us clear.
Just Tohka now.
Something wrong?
No, it's just, when I heard
Origami say she loved Shido,
I felt my chest squeezing tight right here.
Saving Shido should be my priority, but...
...I can't stop thinking about this feeling.
These silly thoughts get in the way.
That's not some silly thought at all.
Yeah. It's the most important
feeling you'll need to save Shido.
To save Shido?
Go on. We're counting on you, Tohka.
R-Right!
That's weird... Wasn't that
drink earlier alcohol-free?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Shido!
Tohka? That's impressive...
I figured you'd be getting hungry!
I brought all the tasty foods
with me! Shall we eat?
Y-Yeah. Thank...
Shido?!
--Shido!
--What? What happened?
--Not good. It happened sooner than we thought
--You okay, Shido? Get a hold--
--Get away... from me... Tohka!
Flashing... Thunder...
...Wave!
Shido!
There's abnormal Spirit waves
pouring out of Shido!
His Spirit powers are off the charts!
All of his emotion readings
are unreadable! He's on a rampage!
Spatial quake alarm, full danger!
At this rate, we'll have an even worse
disaster than the one 30 years ago!
Kotori, what are you doing?!
We have to stop him!
Emergency. It's a race against time!
All right... I'll deal with him.
In case this ever happened,
and to eliminate Shido when it did
is why Ratatoskr made Dainsleif.
I'm sorry, big brother...
Forgive me for having no way out but this...
Origami?
You must never use this.
We'll all find a way somehow.
Origami is right. You're not alone, Kotori.
There's Origami and me,
Kaguya, Yuzuru, Yoshino,
Miku, and Natsumi, too.
If we put our powers together,
I know we can save Shido.
Tohka... Origami... Right.
If we don't slow Shido down
somehow, we'll never catch up!
Is that even possible?
What can we do?
I can be so whimsical sometimes...
What happened? This is our chance!
We won't have long to make it count!
Relax. It's long enough for the speedy Yamai.
Raphael, El Re'em!
Response. Raphael, El Nahash!
Shido, we'll save you.
Grateful. Just like you saved us back then.
We'll save you soon, Shido.
A-Are you happy now?
Aww, you didn't even make it a good one!
That's an indirect kiss with Natsumi!
What's that?
Metatron.
--Kotori!
--Big brother, I'm sorry!
Shido!
Shido! Your final opponent is me!
Tohka...
We're outta time! Hurry!
Her power's gone?!
--Tohka!
--Stay back!
Don't... interfere!
I feel like...
...I have to do this on my own!
Shido...
Have you always been fighting
this pain and fear this whole time?
Why didn't you stop moving forward?
How were you able to keep reaching out
in order to save all of us?
Oh, I see...
This must be the feeling
that everyone calls love.
But it's different than
my love for the others...
It's a love just for Shido.
That's why I...
Shido...
Hey, Tohka. Sure you don't want me to do it?
No, I'm good.
I'm the only one who didn't
get you to fall for me.
So...
Tohka...
All done, Shido!
Tasty?
Mmm, it is.
Did your heart skip a beat?
Yeah, it totally did.